Guide to the Stanford University, Sponsored Projects Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Sponsored Projects Office, records
1960-1988
SC0344
Stanford University. Sponsored Projects Office.
53.5 Linear feet
Records from the Sponsored Projects Office include correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, patent files, and financial records.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfers, 1983-1993.
Information about Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use.
Scope and Content of Collection
Records from the Sponsored Projects Office pertain to administrative matters and to individual projects; included are correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, patent files, and financial records. Many of the correspondence files are those of Earl Cilley. Specific topics include the Solar Energy Research Institute, 1976-77; the BALLOTS project, 1975; the NIRT project; the Te Vega research ship; the Stanford Electronics Laboratory; the San Joaquin Basin Analysis Project; indirect cost recovery; the Committee on Research; and the Committee on Government Relations.
Access Terms
Solar Energy Research Institute.; Te Vega.; Education, Higher--Research.; Federal aid to research.; Research--California--Stanford University.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1983-158
  Accession 1983-158 includes records related to the Solar Energy Research Institute, 1976-77, and the BALLOTS project 1975.
  - Solar Energy Research Institute [SERI], correspondence and report, 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SERI - discussion on proposal, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - SERI - miscellany (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SERI, site visit planning meeting, Berkeley, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - SERI, cost proposal briefing, Burbank, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - SERI, correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - SERI, responses to questions (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - SERI, proposal, vol. 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - SERI, proposal, final volumes 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - SERI, correspondence, (after 10/1/76) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - SERI, coordinating committee meeting, Berkeley, 9/27/76 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SERI miscellaneous news reports (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - SERI correspondence and proposal drafts (4) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - SERI correspondence and proposal drafts (3) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - SERI correspondence and proposal drafts (2) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - SERI correspondence and proposal drafts prior, 4/76 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Solar Energy Research Associates (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - SERI proposal, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Center for Information Processing annual reports (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - BALLOTS advisory board (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - BALLOTS center plan (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - BALLOTS center business plan final draft (copy #3) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - BALLOTS correspondence (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - BALLOTS newsletter (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - BALLOTS project, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - BALLOTS miscellaneous info and reprints (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - BALLOTS Center - drafts (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - BALLOTS Center - drafts (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - [BALLOTS miscellaneous] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - BALLOTS Plan - final review (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1986-200
  Accession 1986-200 consists of records pertaining to general administrative issues as well as specific projects, 1960-79.
  - Subject File Index (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academy for Education Development (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Senate, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Conference of the United States, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adm. Panel on Animal Care Report, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Panel on Radiological Hazards Control, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Review of Faculty Employment Relationship (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Review of Faculty Employment Relationship, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Committee on Research NSF, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Panel on Safety and Health, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Agency for International Development, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Cancer Society, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Council on Education, 1966-73 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Heart Association RA, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Audits, (Prior to 9/76) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Augsburger, Robert, (1977 and Earlier) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Rogers, R. Veaner, Libraries, BALLOTS Project, OEG-1-7-071145-4428 USOE (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Veaner, A. B., University Libraries, BALLOTS, OEG-0-70-5237 Current, (1971) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Audit Information Exchange, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bell Educational Services, Inc., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Benefits Study, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Biohazards, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Business Monthly Summaries, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - California, State of, Dept. of Benefits Payment, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - DNA (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, older than 9/77 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 9/77 - 8/78 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - DNA General (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Recombinant DNA: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Guidelines for Research Involving Recombinant DNA Molecules (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DHEW - Assurance: Sex Discrimination, 1972-75 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - DHEW: General (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - DHEW: Grantee Management Proposal (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - DHEW: Institutional Cost Sharing Agreement, 1966-75 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - DHEW: NIE (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - DHEW/NIH: Central Indirect Cost Management, 1970-71 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - DHEW/NIH: Consortium Grants, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - DHEW/NIH: Manpower Survey, 1974-75 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - DHEW/NIH: Renewal Application Control, 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1962-77 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Djerassi: Mass Spectrometer, 1963-68 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Economic Stabilization Program (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ECRC: Workshop Oklahoma State, February 10 - 11, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ECRC: General (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - ECRC: Research Administration Workshop, University of Mississippi, February 21-23, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Effort Reporting (Federal Interest Agency Taskforce), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Emeritus Faculty, 1967-73 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Engineering, School of, 1966-75 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (California Transport Control Plan), 1972-75 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1971-74 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Equal Opportunity and Compliance, 1964-72 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Equipment Title, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ERDA, Audit, SLAC/PEP, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ERDA, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ERDA: University Programs Advisory Panel (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Expenditure Ceiling (NSF), 1973-75 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Faculty, 1972-75 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Effort Reporting, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Federal Supply Code for Nonmanufacture (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fellowships, 1965-74 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Financial Reports: Forecasting and Data, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Financial Reports: Forecasting and Data, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Financial Reports: Forecasting and Data, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Foundation, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Foundation, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gale Research Center, 1963-68 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - General (NSF), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1973-75 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1963-74 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - General Electric Company (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 232-79-0053, University of San Francisco: William C. Fowkes, Family, Community and Preventative Medicine (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Snow, Richard E., Education 10/78, N00014-79-C-0171 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - DAA629-78-C-0047: Army, C.W. Frank (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - DAS660-77-C-0073: SEL, Flynn (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - DA903-76-C-0206: ARPA, Defense Supply Service, McCarthy (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - File re research project on Fundamental Properties of the Ionosphere (O. Villard and others) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hansen Labs, 1965-73 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hansen Labs: Estimates of Indirect Cost Rebates due as of, August 31, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Harbridge House, Inc., 1968-71 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hayflick, Dr. Leonard, 1969-70 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - DHEW: Freeze, 5/68 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - DHEW: Public Health Service: General, 1964-66 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - DHEW: Public Health Service: General, 1960-63 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), 1973-75 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), 1967-74 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Gibbons Patent (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Gifts, 1968-72 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Goals and Objectives, 1973-74 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Goals and Objectives, 1974-76 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Goals and Objectives, 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Goals and Objectives, [empty], 1977-78 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Goals and Objectives, [empty], 1978-79 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Goals and Objectives, [empty], 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Government Contracts for Academic Instruction and Training Contracts, 1968-71 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Government: Federal Procurement (51437), 1970-75 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Government Property, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Government Property, 1972-74 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Government Property (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Government Relations, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Grants (non-gov), 1972-73 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Grievances, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Guide Memos, 1973-74 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 14-08-001-18380, USGS Civil Engineering, G.W. Clough (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Tyack, David, NIE 400-78-0042: "Conference...Historical Study...Education and Work" (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Hoover Institution, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Institution, PL 93-585, (1975) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 1962-74 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 1972-73 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hospital, 1964-74 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - HUD (Department of Housing and Urban Development), 1968-74 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Indirect Cost, 1971-75 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Indirect Costs: Additional O/H Recovery from NIH, 1971-75 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Indirect Costs: DOD/DHEW Agreements, 1965-75 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Indirect Costs: Rebates, 1976-77 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Aeroacoustics, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Defense Analysis, 1967-68 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - IMSSS, 1967-73 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Public Policy Analysis: temporary, 1969-72 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Institute for the Study of Human Problems, 1966-70 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Institutional Patent Agreement (NSF), 1973-74 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Interchange Personnel Agreements, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Interior, Department of, 1968-74 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - International Business Machines, 1962-74 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Intergovernmental Personnel Act of 1970, Personnel Mobility Assignment Agreements, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - IPAS (PHS Institutional Prior Approval System), 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - IPAS (PHS Institutional Prior Approval System), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Justice, Department of, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - JSEP Speech, University of Southern California, April 9, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - King-Hurley Research Group, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Labor, Department of, 1971-73 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Labor: Bargaining Unit Composition (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Labor: Committee Notes (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Labor: Contract Communication Group (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Labor: External Communications, August, 1974-75 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Labor: Fair Labor Standards Act, US3F (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Labor: Position Papers (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Labor: General, 1976-77 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Labor: General, 1970-73 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Labor: Interest Groups (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Labor: Working Conditions (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Labor: Strike Contingency Planning (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Labor: Planning and Coordination Group (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Labor: Science Interest Group, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Language and Area Center, 1971-73 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Large Contract Research Centers Group, 1965-69 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Law School, 1970-72 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lockheed Aircraft Corporation, 1965-72 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mailing List and Photographic Reproduction Information, 1970-74 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1969-71 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Massy Memos, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Memoranda: General, 1973-74 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Minority Education, 1968-70 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - NASA, 1964-67 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - NASA, 1970-74 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - NASA: Memoranda of Understanding, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - NACUBO [National Association of College and University Business Officers], 1971-75 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - NACUBO: College and University Business Administration, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - NACUBO: Committee on Government Relations, 1963-64 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1970-73 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - National Committee on Financing Postsecondary Education, 1973-74 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - National Council of University Research Administrators (NCURA), 1972-75 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - National Institutes of Health (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - NCURA, 1971-74 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - NCURA, 1960-70 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NCURA: Foundations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NCURA: Membership List, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "NCURA News", 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - National Endowment on Arts and Humanities, 1974-75 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - NSF: Expenditure Ceiling FY, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NSF: Expenditure Ceiling FY, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NSF: Expenditure Ceiling FY, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - NSF, 1974-76 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - NSF, prior to, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - NSF: Grant Administration Manual, 1971-73 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - NSF: Important Notices, 1964-73 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NSF, 1964-67 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - NSF, 1960-63 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NSF: Research Management Improvement Program, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Nepotism, 1971-74 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Act (OSHA), 1973-74 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Office of Business and Finance, 1974-75 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEG): Executive Office of the President, 1963-71 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Office of Management and Budget Circular A-88/A102, 1969-75 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Old Pavilion, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Organization (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Other Universities, 1972-74 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Overdrafts, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Overdrawn Accounts, 1971-72 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Parking Study (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Patent Policy, 1974-75 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Personnel: Affirmative Action, 1972-75 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Personnel: General, 1973-74 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Personnel: Job Descriptions, 1969-75 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Personnel: Salary Guidelines, 1972-73 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Personnel: Mobility, Guidelines for Intergovernmental Personnel Act of, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Physics, Department of, 1963-75 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - SPO Organizational Charts, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SPO Procedures, 1977-79 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Procedures, Functions and Responsibilities, 1976-77 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Procedures, Functions and Responsibilities, 1967-71 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Procedures, Functions and Responsibilities, 1972-75 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Power Lab (GT and E), 1964-71 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - President's Space Study (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Printing Regulations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Privacy, 1973-74 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Privacy Act, 1972-75 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Privacy Act, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Proposal Review Criteria (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Publications and Subscriptions, 1966-73 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Publication, Freedom of (Rights in Technical Data), 1966-74 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Purchasing SPO, 1972-75 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Purchasing, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Radiological Hazards Control Committee, 1970-71 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Rebudgeting Requests, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Records Retention, 1962-74 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Research Advisory Group, 1972-75 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Research Advisory Group, 1972-75 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Research Associates/Assistants, 1972-73 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Resources: Translators (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Research: Army Report on Biological Warfare, March 8, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Research Development Fund (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Research (Iran) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Research, 1969-70 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Research: General (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Research: General (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Responses to Federal Regulation Announcements (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ROTC (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Salaries, 1961-75 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - School Mathematics Study Group (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Script (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - SCRIPT, 1973-75 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - SCRIPT: Portfolio (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - SCRIPT: Review (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sit-in: AEL, April, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Projects Office Annual Report, 1967-75 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Projects Office Goals and Objectives, 1972-75 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Completed SPO Guide Revisions (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - SPO Procedures for Processing non-Governmental Grants and Proposals (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - SPO Project Status, 1972-75 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - SPO Reports and Analyses, 1972-75 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Projects Information Center (SPIC) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Sponsored Projects Office: Tax Information (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Staff Benefits, 1963-75 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Staff Benefit Rates, 1972-73 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Electronics Laboratory (SEL), 1964-74 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - SEL: Radioscience Laboratory, 1964-73 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - SLAC, 1972-74 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - SLAC, 1964-71 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - SLAC: Conflict of interest, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - SLAC: Vehicle Liability Insurance, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - SPIC, 1972-75 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - SPIF/Project on Urban Studies/ASSU (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Stanford School of Medicine, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1965-75 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - SRI Organization Study, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - SWOPSI, 1971-72 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University Petroleum Recovery Institute (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - State Aid to Higher Education, 1969-74 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - State, Department of: Standard Regulations, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - STSA Advisory Council, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - State Technological Services Program: California, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Strike Information File (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Student Aid, 1971-75 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Student Support from Research (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Student Unrest (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Study of Education at Stanford (SES), 1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Surabaya Institute of Technology (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Taxes (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Termination Policy, 1967-70 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Te Vega #1 (HH Files) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Te Vega #2 (HH Files) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Te Vega #3 (HH Files) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Te Vega #4 (HH Files) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Te Vega, NSF G-17465, Indirect Cost Rate, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Te Vega Indirect Cost, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Te Vega Proposal, 1968-69 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Te Vega Cables (HH Files) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Purchase of "PROTEUS" (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Transportation, Department of: Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Travel, 1969-75 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Trustees, Board of: Sig. Resolutions, 1973-74 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Trustees' Signature Authorizations, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Trustees' Signature Authorizations, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Trustees' Signature Authorizations, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Trustees' Signature Authorizations, 1964-71 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - United Stanford Employees, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - University of California: Quality of Management Program (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Universities: other, 1969-75 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Use Allowance Agreements, 1969-73 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - VA Hospital, 1970-73 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Vice Presidential Group, 1972-75 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - W.F. Miller: Vice President for Research (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Western Association of College and University Business Officers, 1969-74 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Word Processing (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - DOD Contract Transfers, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Department of Defense, 1965-75 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - DOD - Air Force - General, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - DOD AFOSR Durand/Skilling, 1968-73 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - DOD - Air Force - W-P Air Force Base Negotiations (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - F18600-73-A-0164 AF Basic Agreement (prev. F44621-A0054) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - F18600-75-A-0164 AF Basic Agreement (prev. F18600-73-A-0164 see Vol. 1) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - DOD - DCAA, 1974-75 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - DOD Publication, Freedom of, 1966-74 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - DOD Defense Documentation Center, 1968-71 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - DOD General, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - DOD - Navy - General, 1964-73 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Office of Naval Research, 1974-75 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Drug Studies, 1979-81 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 9/78-8/79 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 9/79-9/80 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Recombinant DNA - Regulations and Procedures (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Recombinant DNA - Public Comment (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Recombinant DNA - Assurances, Panel, Charges (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - NIH Guidelines for Recombinant DNA Research (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Consulting Policy, 1969-71 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Copyright Policy, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cost Accounting Standards Board, 1975-77 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Cost Accounting Standards Board -, 1977 to present (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Cost Accounting Standards Board - Temporary - EGLC, 1972-75 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - CASB, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - CASB, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - CASB (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Cost Sharing (1), 1970-79 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cost Sharing (2), 1970-79 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Credit Ratings, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Crisis Information Center (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Release of DOD Information Excerpts: Publication Clauses in Contracts (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - DOD Research at Stanford, Vol. 1, Two Perceptions: The Investigator's and the Sponsor's by SWOPSI (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research Memos, (1972-74) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research, (1975) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Center for Materials Research, (1969-75) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Charge Out Rates for University Services, (1973) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Children's Convalescent Hospital Affiliation Agreement, (1974) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Commerce Clearing House, (1969) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Commerce, U. S. Dept. of, (1967-75) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 1202 Commissions, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Government Procurement (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Governmental Relations, (1974-75) (Box 14, Folder 18)